Guide to the New York Bureau of Legal Advice (New York Bureau of Legal First Aid) Records TAM.044
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
New York Bureau of Legal Advice Records
1917-1919
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
New York Bureau of Legal Advice
TAM.044
6.5 Linear Feet in 13 manuscript boxes
The New York Bureau of Legal First Aid was organized in 1917 with a grant from the Women's Peace Party. Lead by attorney Charles Recht and feminist Frances M. Witherspoon, it was the first organization to furnish free legal advice and counsel to anyone who came into conflict with the new laws related to America's entry into World War I, including draft resisters, conscientious objectors, and deserters. By 1918 it was aiding at least 5,000 clients and changed its name to the New York Bureau of Legal Advice (NYBLA). Though raided by the Bureau of Investigation in 1918, the NYBLA continued with its anti-war campaigns until shortly after the Armistice was signed. The records contain correspondence, office files, case histories, photographs, clippings, and press releases relating to selective service exemption, draft evasion, conscientious objector status, military discharge, desertion, amnesty, civil liberties and deportation.
Custodial History
The 1917-1919 records of the New York Bureau of Legal Advice had been stored at the Tamiment Institute Library among old file boxes and cartons relating to World War I. In 1961 Professor Martin David Dubin of Roosevelt University borrowed the collection to began researching, and ulitmately processing, the records of the Bureau. He returned the collection to Tamiment Library in 13 document boxes (5.5 linear feet) in 1970. The accession numbers 1961.001 and 1961.002 are associated with this collection.
A large fragment of the Bureau's office files were donated to the Swathmore College Peace Collection at an unknown date. The files at Swathmore are primarily comprised of case files of individual clients. The records at the Tamiment Library include all the central office files, as well as many individual case files.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
The New York Bureau of Legal First Aid was organized on May 11, 1917 with a one hundred dollar grant from the Women's Peace Party. Individuals contributed to the treasury and in August the People's Council, the Socialist Party, the Civil Liberties Bureau and the Workmen's Council all became sponsoring affiliates. A few months later the People's Council and the Civil Liberties Bureau withdrew their support, but a strong Executive Committee continued the organizing work. In May 1918, the organization changed its name to the New York Bureau of Legal Advice (NYBLA). During that year, the Bureau estimated that it aided at least 5,000 clients. In September 1918, a raid by the Federal Bureau of Investigation disrupted organizational functioning temporarily. NYBLA continued with its anti-war campaigns and only ended its work in the autumn of 1919, shortly before the Armistice.
NYBLA was the first organization to furnish free legal advice and counsel to anyone who came into conflict with the new laws related to America's entry into World War I, including draft resisters, conscientious objectors, and deserters. The Bureau sought to gather information and investigate and publicize war-related instances of infringements of First Amendment rights. The Bureau campaigned for amnesty for conscientious objectors and also monitored their treatment in military prisons. Lobbying by NYBLA was instrumental in forcing Secretary of War Newton B. Baker to order an end to the practice of holding conscientious objectors in manacles. The Bureau cooperated actively with the Industrial Workers of the World and other radical groups in defense of free speech and in opposition to the deportation of immigrant radicals.
Charles Recht, a Czech-born attorney, was the General Counsel of the Bureau. As Secretary of the Bureau, Frances M. Witherspoon, an ardent feminist and socialist peace activist, carried on the daily work of the Bureau, including fundraising, working with attorneys and volunteers, organizing lobbying campaigns, maintaining correspondence, and interviewing clients. She worked with the leading socialists, anti-war activists and civil libertarians of the time, including Roger N. Baldwin, Ella Reeve ("Mother") Bloor, M. Eleanor Fitzgerald, Albert De Silver, Jacob Hillquit, and Scott Nearing.
Scope and Content Note
Approximately half of the records of the New York Bureau of Legal Advice consist of case histories pertaining to selective service exemption, draft evasion, conscientious objector status, military imprisonment, military discharge, desertion, amnesty, civil liberties and deportations. Approximately one third of the collection consists of office files, administrative reports and correspondence, including extensive fundraising correspondence. The remainder of the collection is made up of press releases and newspaper clippings.
The case histories, chiefly relating to draft exemption, provide significant and frequently poignant information on the daily lives and problems of the working class immigrants who were the principal clients of the Bureau's pioneering efforts to deliver free legal services and to protect poor people's civil rights. The correspondence and office files reflect civil liberties activity and the Bureau's role as a connecting link between "those on the firing line in anti-war agitation" and America's large and politically diverse peace and socialist movements.
The correspondents to the NYBLA are numerous and varied; many well known progressives of the period made a contribution to the Bureau's work. Among them are Mary Beard, Sarah N. Cleghorn, Elizabeth Gurley and Bina Flynn, Agnes Smedley, Louis Untermeyer, Thorsten Veblen, H. L. Mencken, Sinclair Lewis, Judah L. Magnes, and Stephen Wise.
Arrangement
The collection was arranged by Professor Martin David Dubin of Roosevelt University in the 1960s, and the Tamiment Library maintained his arrangement. The collection is ordered in six series:
I. Office Files
II. Correspondence
III. Case Files: Aliens, Deportations, Special Individuals
IV. Case Files: Conscientious Objectors
V. Case Files: Draft Boards, Aliens, Dependents
VI. Press Releases and Newspaper Clippings
Folders are generally arranged alphabetically by subject/author heading then chronologically within each subject/author heading.
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
The Charles Recht Papers (TAM 176)
American Committee for Protection of Foreign Born Records (TAM 086)
New York Bureau of Legal Advice Collected Records at the Swathmore College Peace Collection (CDG-A)
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Due to the fragile nature of the original materials, researchers must use the microfilmed version; microfilm call number is Film R-7006, Reels 1-10.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred from the Tamiment Institute Library. There is no earlier provenance information. The accession numbers associated with this collection are 1961.001 and 1961.002.
Amnesty |z United States.; Legal aid |z United States.; Deportation |z United States.; Desertion, Military |z United States.; Draft resisters.; Clippings (information artifacts); Case files.; Conscientious objectors |z United States.; New York (N.Y.).; Correspondence.; Minutes (administrative records); Caffey, Francis G. (Francis Gordon), 1868-; DeSilver, Albert, 1888-1924; Baldwin, Roger Nash, 1884-1981; Bloor, Ella Reeve, 1862-1951; Witherspoon, Fannie M.; Recht, Charles.; Nelles, Walter, 1883-1937; Fitzgerald, M. Eleanor (Mary Eleanor), 1877-1955; American Civil Liberties Union; New York Bureau of Legal Advice; League for the Amnesty of Political Prisoners
- Series I: Office Files
  Scope and Content Note
  This series consists of administrative materials such as by-laws, executives' reports, minutes, funding circulars, policy statements, publicity brochures, membership and mailing lists, legal correspondence, government forms, conference materials, drafts and manuscripts, logs of cases, bills, and other office materials.
  - Appeal for Funds, November 1918 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    Reel 7006/1
  - By-Laws, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Circular Letters, 1917-1918 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Conference on Legal Aid, July 18, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Copies of Bills, Laws and Regulations, 1917-1918 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee, Statements by the Committee, 1917-1919 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Forms, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - History and Purposes, ca.1917 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Illegal Conduct of Draft Board Registrars, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Incitement to Violence, April-May 1919 (cf. Box 1, Folder 22, Statement of Ministers) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Instructions for the Second Draft, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lists -- lawyers, donors, members, contacts, politicians, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Minutes, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Manuscripts, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Printed Matter -- circulars, petitions, by-laws, brochures, 1918-1919 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Reports and Correspondence of the Treasurer, 1917-1919 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Reports of Counsel, Charles Recht, 1917-1919 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Resume of Cases Involving Free Speech and Pacifism, 1917-1919 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Secretary's Correspondence, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Secretary's Reports and Statements, 1917-1918 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Statement in Reply to Report of Francis G. Caffey U.S. District Attorney, 1917-1918 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Statement of Ministers, June 1919 (cf. also Box 1, Folder 10, Incitement to Violence) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Series II: Correspondence Files
  This series consists of correspondence with individuals and organizations. Along with individual correspondents' files, there are files of Miscellaneous writers after each alphabetical category. A substantial number of the letters are carbons of Miss Witherspoon's fund raising messages. Her individual appeals to friends of the bureau and assiduous hunt for donations and pledges led her to correspond with such noteworthy supporters as H. L. Mencken, Sinclair Lewis, Louis Untermeyer, Thorsten Veblen, and Upton Sinclair. The correspondence files also show that a strong network of progressive organizations bolstered the NYBLA.
  - American Freedom Convention, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - American Union Against Militarism (cf. also National Civil Liberties Bureau), 1918 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Arbitrator, 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Ashley, Misses Anita and Jessie, 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - A-Miscellaneous A, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Baker, Newton D. U.S. Secretary of War, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Baldwin, Roger N., 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Bloor, Mrs. Ella Reeve, 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Brenner, Anna R., 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Reel 7006/2
  - Burd, Adelma H., 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - B-Miscellaneous B, 1917-1919 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Clark, Evans, 1917-1919 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Coe, George A, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Committee of Forty-Eight, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Conboy, Martin, Director of Draft, New York City, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - C-Miscellaneous C, 1917-1919 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Detroit Organizations, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Draft Boards, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Draft Boards--List of Attorneys, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - D-Miscellaneous D, 1917, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Elliott, Dr. John L., 1917-1919 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - E-Miscellaneous E, 1917-1919 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Fawcett, James Waldo, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation, 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Fitzgerald, M.E., 1918 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - France, Senator Joseph, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - F-Miscellaneous F, 1917-1919 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Guaranty Title & Trust Co., 1917-1919 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - G-Miscellaneous G, 1917-1919 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Hallinan, Charles T., 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Hillquit, Jacob, 1917-1919 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - H-Miscellaneous H, 1917-1919 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - International (Industrial) Workers of the World, 1919 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - I-Miscellaneous I, 1917-1919 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Daily Forward, 1919 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - J-MIscellaneous J, 1917-1919 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Keppel, Fredrick A. 3d Assistant, US Sec'y of War, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - K-Miscellaneous K, 1917-1919 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Lane, Mrs. Margaret, 1917-1919 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - League for the Amnesty of Political Prisoners (cf. also M.E. Fitzgerald), 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - League for Democratic Control, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Legal Advisory Board for New York City, 1917-1918 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Liberty Defense Union, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Reel 7006/3
  - London, Honorable Meyer, 1917-1919 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Lunde, Theo H., 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - L-Miscellaneous L, 1917-1919 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - M-Miscellaneous M, 1917-1919 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Mac-Mc, 1917-1919 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - National Civil Liberties Bureau (cf. also American Union Against Militarism), 1917-1919 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - National Civil Liberties Bureau Defense Fund, 1917-1918 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Nelles, Walter (cf. National Civil Liberties Bureau), 1918 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Neumann, Dr. Henry, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - New York City Board of Aldermen, 1919 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - New York State Militia, 1917-1918 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - N-Miscellaneous N, 1917-1919 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - O-Miscellaneous O, 1917-1919 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - People's Council of America, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Pollitzer, Margaret, and Mrs. Sigmund, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - P-Miscellaneous P, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Radical Press, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Recht, Charles (cf. also Box 1, Folder 17), 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Roe, Gilbert, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - R-Miscellaneous R, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Socialist Party (NY), 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Sorchan, Charlotte, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Sotsky, Louis -- War Stamp Sales, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - S-Miscellaneous S, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Reel 7006/4
  - Teachers' Union, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - T-Miscellaneous T, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - US Department of Justice, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - US Department of War--Adjutant General, 1918-1919 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - US Department of War--Provost Marshal General, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - U-Miscellaneous U, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Villard, Mrs. Henry (Fannie Villard), 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - V-Miscellaneous V, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Weiss, Louis & Co., 1918-1919 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Woman's International League (cf Woman's Peace Party), 1919 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Woman's Peace Party (cf Woman's International League), 1917 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Workers Defense Union, 1918-1919 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - W-Miscellaneous W, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Young Democracy, 1918-1919 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Y-Z Miscellaneous Y Z, 1918-1919 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Series III: Case Files: Aliens, Deportations, Individuals
  This series contains correspondence, affidavits, legal notices, clippings and legal transcripts relating to deportations and other actions threatened by the government against immigrants and opponents of the war effort. Notable among these papers are documents of the Chinese United Association, a Chinatown labor organization, and case files on Gertrude Pignol, a New York City high school teacher dismissed from her position because of her opposition to the war, and on the Italian labor activist Arturo Giovanetti.
  - Fred Cammer, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Ralph Cheyney and Louis C. Fraina, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Theodore Fedotoff and Anton Taichin, 1917-1919 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Arturo Giovanetti, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Nicholas Hourwich, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Ranislaw Jovanovitch, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Louis Kramer, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Charles Kroll, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Nathan Levin, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Frank R. Lopez, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Jacques Mamaux, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - John Meehan, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Samuel Nikition, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Gertrude A.M. Pignol, 1918-1919 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - David Schiff, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Max Vieweiger, 1917? (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Ernest Wadc, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Louis Wepner, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Catherine A. Lowe -- Deportation Fund (cf also Deportation Cases), 1918 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Deportation Cases (cf also Catherine A. Lowe), 1919 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Chinese Deportation Cases, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Austrian Hungarian Aliens, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Russian Aliens, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Court Records, 1918-1919 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    Reel 7006/5
- Series IV: Case Files: Conscientious Objector Files
  The Conscientious Objectors files include correspondence with the CO's and with their families as well as affidavits, court martial records, and correspondence with military officials. Subjects of correspondence include lobbying campaigns, prison brutality, strikes and hunger strikes by prisoners, and the progress of cases. There are also files on the military camps where the COs were incarcerated and photographs of CO's at internment camps at Camp Dix and Fort Riley, Kansas.
  - Committee of Friends of Conscientious Objectors, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Friends of Conscientious Objectors--Correspondence, November 1918-March 1919., 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Friends of Conscientious Objectors--Correspondence; April-May, 1919. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Friends of Conscientious Objectors--Correspondence, June 1919. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Friends of Conscientious Objectors--Correspondence; Jul-Sep 1919 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - General File, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 6A)
  - Rulings, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Camp Lists, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Camp Funston, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Camp Upton, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Fort Douglas, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Fort Leavenworth, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Fort Riley, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Bales, William, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Bauman, Joseph, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Becker, Maurice, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Bernstein, Mayer, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Blair, N.J., 1918 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Block, Hyman, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Brandon, Joseph, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Breger, Benjamin, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Breidert, William, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Briehl, Walter, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Broms, Allan, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Clodi, Charles, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Reel 7006/6
  - DeRosa, Ulysses, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Ding, Oliver, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Donasti, Benjamin, 1918? (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Eichel, David, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Fenkart, Eugene, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Ferguson, William J., 1917-1918 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Fernandez, M.P., 1918 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Gellert, Ernest, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Getts, Clark, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Grass, John (cf also Robinson, Karl), 1918 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Greenblatt, Isidor, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Greenfield, Morris, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Grunzig, Bruno, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Halperin, Samuel, 1917 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Heckler, John, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Hotson, Ronald, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Jacobs, Lewis, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Jasmagy, William (Clarence), 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Kreoris, Stalius, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Kroop, Isidore, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Lassen, Knud, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Lee, Harry, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Longwell, Joseph, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Lunde, Erling (cf. Theo Lunde, Box 3, Folder 16), 1919 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - McNamara, Michael, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Monsky, Henry, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Moore, Howard, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Platin, Eric, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Prezner, Ralph, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Robinson, Karl (cf also Grass, John), 1918 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Salmon, Benjamin, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Sanjour, Michael, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Seidenberg, Roderick, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Stepanovitch, Fritz, 1917 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Volsky, Joseph, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - White, Joseph, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Series V: Case Files: Draft Boards, Aliens, Dependents
  Most of the individual cases in these files concern the working class clients of the NYBLA. Correspondence with clients and families, affidavits, and correspondence with military officials are included in this series. Their requests for excuse from military service usually concerned their immigrant status or their family responsibilities.
  - A-General, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Aldino, John, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Altschuler, Uriah, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Angelus, John, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Arminio, Antonio, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Arola, John, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Artmenkl, Andrew, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Ashendorf, Harry, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - B-General, 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Reel 7006/7
  - Bennett, Julius, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Becker, Emanuel, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Bernstein, Morris, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Bieker, Joseph, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Blau, Isaak, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Bodner, Max, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Brenner, Meyer, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Brickman, Israel, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - C-General, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Cabet, Adolph, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Cahn, Ralph, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Caine, Jack, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Cane, Jacob, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Carciopolo, Vito, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Chodosh, Harry, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Cohen, Charles, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Cohen, George, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Cohen, Hyman, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Cohen, Myer, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Cohen, Phillip, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Cohen, Sam, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Corbin, Abe, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Coronel, Jean, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - D-General, 1917-1919 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Davis, Benjamin, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Diamond, Luper, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Duffy, James, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - E-General, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Egnatovich, Steve, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Eiges, David, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Eldridge, John, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Elkin, Harry, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - F-General, 1917-1919 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Feinstein, Harry, undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Forman, Benjamin, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Frank, Sam, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Freudenrich, William, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Fried, Nathan, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Friedman, David, 1917-1918 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - G-General, 1917-1919 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Ginther, William, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Goldberg, David and Tobias, 1917-1918 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Glaser, Isidore, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Glick, David, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Grass, George, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Greenfield, Morris, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - H-General, 1917-1918 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Halpern, Harry, 1918 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Hannula, Frank, 1918 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Hauser, Louis, 1918 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Heikkinen, A., 1918 (Box 9, Folder 5)